

MY CONTACT

Phone +63961 393 0468

Email

roneilalgara@gmail.com

Address

Progreso Village, Block 118 Lotb 33, Arao, Vista Alegre, Bacolod City, Philippines

EXPERTISE

- Web Development
- NodeJS
- ReactJS
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- Coding
- UX Design

REFERENCES

Engr. Alexander Diamante

Department-in-charge, ECE Dept. TUP V

Phone

+639998162269

Engr. Amelito Raymunda

Area Supervisor

Phone

+639469478568

RONEIL ALGARA

WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT MYSELF

Solution-driven web developer, adept at contributing to highly collaborative work environment and finding solutions. Proven experience developing consumer-focused websites using HTML, CSS and JavaScript with ReactJS and NodeJS Framework. Good knowledge of the best practices for web design and user experience.

EXPERIENCE

Web Development BootCamp I May 2023 - July 2023

Full Stack Web Development

- Provided front-end development website using ReactJS.
- Determined coding requirements for specialized scripts.
- Used HTML, CSS, JavaScript, NodeJS, ReactJS and MongoDB for fullstack web development.

Freelance Tutor I 2021 - 2023

- · create graphic designs for learning materials
- · completed all kinds of administrative work
- prepare and record the minutes of the meeting

Transmission Specialists Inc. I 2019 - 2022

Operations Engineer

- Performs day to day encoding job
- enters data to the system accurately
- maintain day to day operations
- maintain and update website for daily article
- creates design for the online advertising

EDUCATION

2013-2018

Technological University of the Philippines Bachelor of Science in Electronics Engineering